smaloans.com 2014-11-14

# Privacy Policy | LOANS

Privacy Policy  
Your privacy is important to us. To protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.  
Collection and Use of Personal Information  
smaloans.com never sells or shares any information that we obtain from visitors or registered users of our web sites to other organizations or companies. When you request information, register using one of our forms, or contact us offline, we may need your specific information in order to process your registration/request and reply to your needs promptly. We may ask you for contact information (such as your name, email and address). We may also collect demographic and profile data (which users provide to us) at our site and in our databases. We use this data to customize your online experience with smaloans.com and develop and distribute content that we think you might be interested in. In general, we use identifiable information to complete a transaction, as indicated below.  
Protecting Personal Information  
All information provided to smaloans.com -including credit card transactions- is transmitted using SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption. SSL is a proven coding system that lets your browser automatically encrypt, or scramble, data before you send it to us. We also protect account information by placing it on a secure portion of our Site that is only accessible by certain qualified employees of smaloans.com. Furthermore, all of the customer transactional data we collect is protected against unauthorized access with the use of digital certificates. Digital certificates for smaloans.com are issued by VeriSign, one of the most established signers of digital certificates. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure. While we strive to protect your information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of such information.  
Log Files  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocal) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. For general reporting purposes in our SEO Tools, we collect and use the data contained in log files from some of our SEO Tools.  
Cookies and Web Beacons  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.  
We also use third party advertisements on smaloans.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.  
You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.  
Email Policy  
smaloans.com does not send unsolicited commercial email to individuals with whom they do not have consent/permission or a pre-existing or current business relationship. smaloans.com provides all email recipients with a clear, easy and effective method to unsubscribe to any and all online communications.  
Links to Other Sites  
This site links to other sites. smaloans.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. We will not pass your information along to the linked site; however, we cannot protect the information you provide to that site.  
Any other questions or concerns can be directed to: smaloans.com

This paper does not open.
